http://www.mcelroy.com/en/privacypolicy.htm

Click here to learn more about McElroy's response to COVID-19.
Language
English
Español
Buy Equipment Rent Equipment Parts Finder Vault™ Login Distributor Login
Selecting
a Machine?
Socket Fusion Tooling
McElroy Socket Tooling offers the perfect method for the installation of fittings on small diameter pipe.
Learn More
Sidewinder® Machines
The Sidewinder gives you the ability to fuse branch saddles, tapping tees and service saddle fittings.
Learn More
Manual Butt Fusion Machines
McElroy's manual machines offer a compact and light-weight solution for butt fusing pipe.
Acrobat 180
A versatile machine designed for butt fusion of 63mm to 180mm (2" IPS to 6" DIPS) pipe and fittings.
Learn More
Acrobat™ 250
A compact design for tight indoor work
spaces, the 250 fuses pipe and fittings from 63mm - 250mm (2"- 10”).
Learn More
Acrobat™ 315
Compact design for easy maneuvering in tight indoor work spaces specific to the polypropylene industry.
Polygon™
One machine for miter, butt and socket fusion.
Learn More
Explore Product Pages
Polygon™
DynaMc® HP (Hand Pump)
A compact butt fusion
machine that features hand-pump hydraulics to power the carriage operations
Learn More
DynaMc® EP (Electric Pump)
A common HPU (hydraulic
power unit) powers this DynaMc lineup and works with any of the EP machines
Learn More
DynaMc® Auto
The 250 and 412 DynaMcs
are available as automatic units that operate within British Gas and water
The 14 and 26 models are
compact and lightweight, with size ranges from 1" IPS - 6" DIPS
(32mm - 180mm)
Learn More
Medium Diameter
Made for the ditch, the
tough and rugged Pit Bulls 28 to 500 cover 2" IPS - 20" OD (63mm -
Covering 2" IPS to
20" OD (63mm - 500mm), the rolling machines have been the industry
standard since 1975
Learn More
MegaMc®
Powerful machines that
bring versatility to large-diameter jobs from 8" IPS - 65" OD (225mm
- 1600mm)
A
self-contained, self-propelled solution to jobsites from 8" IPS - 48"
OD (225mm - 1200mm)
Powerful
machines that bring versatility to large-diameter jobs from 8" IPS -
65" OD (225mm - 1600mm)
Our
largest machine to date brings a revolutionary new way to fuse large-diameter
Selecting
a Machine?
Socket Fusion Kits
McElroy Socket Tooling
offers the perfect method for the installation of fittings on small diameter
pipe.
Learn More
Spider™ 125
A quick and accurate
socket fusion tool that allows one operator to align, heat, fuse and cool the
pipe.
Learn More
SmartFab™ 125
The SmartFab is a portable
benchtop machine for prefabricating on the jobsite or in the shop.
Hornet™
The Hornet is an industry-first, all-in-one tool for polypropylene outlet fusion.
Learn More
Hornet™ XL
An all-in-one tool outlet fusion tool for branches up to 160mm and main sizes 110mm and larger.
Polygon™
One machine for miter, butt and socket fusion.
Made for fusing pipe from
63mm - 315mm (2" - 12") overhead, vertically and in the tightest
locations.
Learn More
Large Diameter
Lightweight, modular components with upper and lower jaws that can be assembled around the pipe by hand.
Acrobat™ 560/630
DynaMc® EP (Electric Pump)
The 412 combines the features of
popular larger machines into smaller units for use in compact jobsites.
When space
is at a premium, the 618 or 500 Pit Bull fuse 6" IPS - 20" OD (180mm
- 500mm) pipe.
Covering 2" IPS
to 18" OD (63mm - 450mm), the rolling machines have been the industry
standard since 1975.
Learn More
MegaMc®
Powerful machines
that bring versatility to large-diameter jobs from 8" IPS - 24" OD
(225mm - 630mm).
20" OD (63mm - 500mm) pipe -
recognized for its all-terrain, self-contained design.
Learn More
Large Diameter
Self-contained, self-propelled solution to jobsites from 8" IPS -
24" OD (225mm - 630mm).
Powerful machines
that bring versatility to large-diameter jobs from 8" IPS - 24" OD (225mm
- 630mm).
Hot Tap Tools
Looking for facer blades, heater plates and other accessories? Find them on the fusion machine pages.
Show me
QuickCamp™ with 630 Carriage
A lighted, insulated and climate-controlled enclosure for 8" IPS to 24" OD pipe fusion.
Learn More
QuickCamp™ with 900 Carriage
A lighted, insulated and climate-controlled enclosure for 12" IPS to 36" OD pipe fusion.
PolyHorse®
A more productive way to store and handle 3" IPS to 20" OD pipe on the jobsite.
Learn More
MegaMc® PolyHorse®
Boost productivity and promote safer working conditions when working with 20" to 48" OD pipe.
Low Profile Rollers
Two sizes of rollers allow pipe to be pulled around a curve and over considerable distances.
Learn More
Pipe Stands
Save wear and tear on machinery, reduces strain on operators and makes the fusion process easier.
Learn More
PolyPorter®
The advantages of a dolly and functionality of a pipe stand create one of the most useful pipeline tools.
DataLogger® 6
Ruggedized, Android-powered tablet that records and documents key parameters of the fusion process.
Learn More
Vault™
Safely and securely store and analyze DataLogger fusion joint records in the cloud.
In Field® Tensile Tester
Conduct quick and easy qualitative tests of joints on the jobsite using coupons from 2" OD and larger.
Learn More
Guided Side Bend Tester
Test the ductility of pipe fusion joints in a safe, quick manner by replicating a traditional "bend back" test.
Learn More
Test Caps
Designed for quick and easy air pressure testing of polyethylene pipe.
Underground / Construction
The most precise and economical way to tap through 2" IPS - 6" IPS and 63mm - 160mm branch saddles.
Learn More
Mechanical / HVAC / Plumbing
Designed for 32mm - 63mm (1" - 2") Polypropylene Pipe & Fittings.
2" IPS LineTamer®
Quickly straighten and install 2" IPS pipe.
Learn More
3" - 6" IPS LineTamer®
Quickly straighten and install 3" - 6" IPS pipe.
Custom Training
What is Fusion?
DynaMc®
HP (Hand Pump)
Learn More
DynaMc®
EP (Electric Pump)
Talon™ 2000
Need Help Selecting a Machine?
DynaMc®
DynaMc® EP (Electric Pump)
MegaMc® 824
Need Help Selecting a Machine?
Custom Training
What is Fusion?
McElroy Online Privacy Policy Agreement
McElroy Manufacturing, Inc., (McElroy), is committed to keeping any and
all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website
and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential,
secure and private.
THEREFORE, this Privacy Policy
Agreement shall apply to McElroy Manufacturing, Inc., and thus it shall govern
any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of
www.mcelroy.com
you are herein consenting to the following data procedures expressed within this
agreement.
Collection of Information
This website collects various types of information, such as:
Voluntarily provided information which may
include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card
information etc., which may be used when you purchase products and/or services
and to deliver the services you have requested.
Information automatically collected when
visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking
technologies and server logs.
Please rest assured that this site shall only collect personal
information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys,
completed membership forms, and emails. It is the intent of this site to use
personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional
uses specifically provided on this site. McElroy Manufacturing, Inc. may also
gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type
of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality
service.
Use of Information Collected
McElroy Manufacturing, Inc. may collect and may make use of personal
information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of
the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use
personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other
possible products and/or services that may be available to you from
www.mcelroy.com.  McElroy Manufacturing,
Inc. may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or
research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future
services that may be offered. McElroy Manufacturing, Inc. does not now, nor
will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or
names to any third parties.
Unsubscribe or Opt-Out
All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue
receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue
receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or
unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to
marketing@mcelroy.com. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third
party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or
opt-out.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. McElroy
Manufacturing, Inc. does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy
policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we
encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to
read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally
identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies
only and solely to the information collected by our website.
Security
McElroy Manufacturing, Inc. shall endeavor and shall take every
precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security
with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent
any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user's
personal information under our control.
Changes to Privacy Policy
Agreement
McElroy Manufacturing, Inc. reserves the right to update and/or change
the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those change to our
website homepage at
www.mcelroy.com, so that our users and/or visitors are
always aware of the type of information we collect, how it will be used, and under
what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information. If at any point
in time McElroy Manufacturing, Inc. decides to make use of any personally
identifiable information on file, in a manner vastly different from that which
was stated when this information was initially collected, the user or users
shall be promptly notified by email. Users at that time shall have the option
as to whether or not to permit the use of their information in this separate
manner.
Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within this Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in
agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from providing
any Personal Information on this web site.  If you choose not to provide Personal
Information on this site, you may not be able to do certain things, like access
particular areas of the site, download programs, or request product
information. In addition, your continued use of our website following the
posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that
you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Privacy Policy
Agreement related to our website, please feel free to contact us at the
following email, telephone number or mailing address.
Email: privacypolicy@mcelroy.com
Telephone Number: (918) 836-8611
Mailing Address:
McElroy Manufacturing, Inc.
PO Box 580550
Tulsa, Oklahoma 74158
If you do not want to be contacted in the future or would like us to use
your Personal Information for a specified purpose only, or would like us to
correct or update your Personal Information in our records, please contact our
marketing department at marketing@mcelroy.com.
05/25/2018
Copyright ©
McElroy Manufacturing · Patent Information
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience. By using our site, you acknowledge that you have read and understand our Privacy Policy, our Terms and Conditions, and agree to the continued use of cookies on this site.
I agree
×
Close
×
Close
Download
